const QUESTIONS = {
    "3":{
        "1":{
            "question":"Find the pet animal",
            "options": [
                ['ATC'],
                ['TAC'],
                ['CTA']
            ],
            "answer":"2",
            "fact":"fact 1"
        },
        "2":{
            "question":"Animal that gives milk",
            "options": [
                ['WCO'],
                ['CWO'],
                ['WOC']
            ],
            "answer":"3",
            "fact":"fact 2"
        },
        "3":{
            "question":"Find the animal",
            "options": [
                ['GIP'],
                ['IGP'],
                ['GPI']
            ],
            "answer":"1",
            "fact":"fact 3"        
        },
        "4":{
            "question":"Which is a cunning animal",
            "options": [
                ['XFO'],
                ['FXO'],
                ['XOF']
            ],
            "answer":"3",
            "fact":"fact 4"    
        }
    },
    "4":{
        "5":{
            "question":"King of the jungle",
            "options": [
                ['IONL'],
                ['NOIL'],
                ['ILON']
            ],
            "answer":"2",
            "fact":"fact 5"
        },
        "6":{
            "question":"Find the animal",
            "options": [
                ['EERD'],
                ['EDER'],
                ['REED']
            ],
            "answer":"3",
            "fact":"fact 6" 
        },
        "7":{
            "question":"Find the animal",
            "options": [
                ['EBRA'],
                ['RAEB'],
                ['REBA']
            ],
            "answer":"2",
            "fact":"fact 7"  
        },
        "8":{
            "question":"Find the animal",
            "options": [
                ['ERAH'],
                ['RAHE'],
                ['RHEA']
            ],
            "answer":"1",
            "fact":"fact 8"  
        }
    },
    "5":{
        "9":{
            "question":"Find the animal",
            "options": [
                [''],
                [''],
                ['']
            ],
            "answer":"",
            "fact":"fact 9"
        },
        "10":{
            "question":"Find the animal",
            "options": [
                [''],
                [''],
                ['']
            ],
            "answer":"",
            "fact":"fact 10"
        },
        "11":{
            "question":"Find the animal",
            "options": [
                [''],
                [''],
                ['']
            ],
            "answer":"",
            "fact":"fact 11"            
        },
        "12":{
            "question":"Find the animal",
            "options": [
                [''],
                [''],
                ['']
            ],
            "answer":"",
            "fact":"fact 12"
        }
    }

}

module.exports = Object.freeze(QUESTIONS)